The New Akatsuki
（長門）みんな戦いに
疲れてきてるね。
Everyone is growing weary
of fighting.
（弥彦）あぁ。
Yes…
戦いに勝ったって
暁には報酬も何もねえ。
Even if we win,
the Akatsuki doesn't receive
any rewards…
あるのは　ただ理想だけ。
The only things we have
are our ideals.
いつか　たまった疲労は
その理想を消してくだろうよ。
In time, pent-up weariness
will erase that ideal.
みんな何のために戦ってるのか
それを忘れるっていうのか？
Are you saying that everyone will
soon forget what they're fighting for?
長門　お前が暁のリーダーに
なってくれないか？
Nagato…
Will you become the leader
of the Akatsuki?
え？
俺は　リーダーなんて器じゃねえんだ。
Huh?
I'm not…cut out to be a leader.
あのとき…。
That day…
初めて人を刺した。
I killed someone for the first time.
その感触がこの手に残ってて→
The feeling of that moment
hasn't left these hands.
俺は　それだけでブルッてる。
And I can't stop trembling!
弥彦…。
Yahiko…
だけど　お前は違う。
But you're different.
お前には英雄の印がある。
You have the mark of a hero…
輪廻眼という特別な印が。
A special symbol known
as the Rinnegan…
それが
みんなの新しい理想となる。
that will become
everyone's new ideal.
弥彦　俺の輪廻眼を利用するのか？
Yahiko!
Are you going to take advantage
of my Rinnegan?
俺は自分が怖いんだ。
I'm scared of myself.
ずっと　この眼のせいで
苦しんできた。
I've suffered so long because
of these eyes.
わかってる。
I know…
だがお前には
その力を制御する存在がいる。
But you have someone who can
keep that power in check for you.
小南は　ずっと　お前のそばにいる。
Konan will always be at your side.
弥彦…。
Yahiko…
（鳩助）兄貴　大変だ！
どうした？
Hey, Brother! Big news!
What's going on?
半蔵の使者が来た。
A messenger from Hanzo is here.
（勘蔵）そなたが暁のリーダー
弥彦殿か？
Are you Yahiko,
the leader of the Akatsuki?
Yes, I am.
あぁ　そうだ。
I am Kanzo, a trusted friend
of Hanzo of the Salamander.
拙者は　山椒魚の半蔵の腹心
勘蔵と申す。
そなたたち　暁の噂は
かねがね聞いておる。
I've heard many rumors
about you Akatsuki…
武力に頼らぬ
平和主義を貫いているとか。
How you seek peace without
relying on military weapons.
それが俺たち暁の理念だ。
That is the Akatsuki's founding principle.
半蔵より
親書を預かってまいりました。
Hanzo asked me to deliver
a confidential letter to you.
Please…
これを。
これは本当なのか？
Is he serious?
He would like to
meet you personally.
そなたらと
じかにお会いしたいと。
半蔵は　暁をお認めになった。
Hanzo has given the Akatsuki
his seal of approval.
（勘蔵）いずれ半蔵は
そなたたちに→
In time…
Hanzo will leave you to handle
the peace negotiations
雨隠れを囲む三国の和平交渉を
任せるつもりでもいる。
between the three nations
that surround the Hidden Rain.
（鳩助）三国の交渉役って
すげぇぜ　兄貴！
Handle the negotiations
between the three nations…?
That's amazing, Brother!
この話　承知したと
半蔵様に伝えてくれ。
Please relay to Lord Hanzo
that I accept.
（みんな）うぉ～っ！
（鳩助）これで俺たちも
堂々と人助けができる！
That means we can help people
out in the open!
ここに来るまで
多くの犠牲を払ってきた。
So many gave their lives
for us to get to this point.
やっと　その連中に
顔向けができる。
Finally, we'll be able to
face them with pride.
弥彦　キミの相手の痛みを
わかろうとする思いが→
Yahiko, your determination to free others
from pain reached Hanzo.
半蔵に届いたんだよ。
見てごらんよ。
Look…
暁は理想を取り戻した。
The Akatsuki's ideals
have been restored.
印なんて必要なかったんだよ。
There was never a need
for a symbol.
みんな　キミの理想に
どこまでもついていく。
We'll all follow your dream,
no matter where that leads us.
長門…。
Nagato…
俺たちは間違ってなかった。
We weren't wrong!
明日の半蔵様との会合は
俺と長門で行く。
Nagato and I will go to
the meeting tomorrow with Lord Hanzo.
大丈夫かよ　兄貴
俺たちも一緒に…。
Are you sure, Brother?
We'll all go with you…
No, that's not necessary.
いや　大丈夫だ。
俺たちが大挙して→
Lord Hanzo will be shocked if
too many of us show up.
押しかけたら
半蔵様も　ビックリしちまう。
確かに　そうだけど。
I know, but…
そういえば小南は？
By the way, where's Konan?
急きょ第七地区の
見回りに行ってる。
She went to patrol
the Seventh Ward.
明日の朝まで帰らない。
She won't be back until
tomorrow morning.
そうか　せっかくの日なのに。
I see… On such a special day too.
とにかく暁は今日
大きな一歩を記した！
Anyway… Today, the Akatsuki took
a giant step forward!
みんな　今日は
任務を忘れ　無礼講だ！
Everyone! Set aside your duties
for today and celebrate!
（みんな）お～っ！
（半蔵）暁の小僧たちには
気づかれてはいまいな？
The Akatsuki brats aren't suspicious
at all, are they?
（ダンゾウ）もちろんだ。
Of course not.
弥彦とかいう小僧が死ねば
暁は自然消滅するだろう。
If the one called Yahiko is killed,
the Akatsuki will naturally die off.
And what of your plans?
そちらの首尾は？
心配無用。
No need to worry.
（小南）誰が？
Who could have…?
（小南）これは！
This is…!
（半蔵）今頃　人質を
確保している頃だ。
We should be securing
the hostage right about now.
これで里を脅かす
不逞の輩は消え→
With this, that lawless gang that
threatens the village will disappear,
雨隠れは貴殿のものだ。
and the Hidden Rain will be yours.
やっと　ここまで来た。
We finally made it up to this point.
長門。
Nagato.
お前は！？
You're—!
Reality is moving ahead quickly.
現実が大きく動き出している。
今すぐ弥彦たちと手を切り
俺と行動をともにしろ。
Cut your ties with Yahiko immediately
and join me.
でなければ　お前たちは…。
Otherwise, you will all…
俺たちが何だ！？
We will what?
弥彦の言っていることは
ただの理想だ。
What Yahiko speaks of
are just ideals.
相手の痛みをわかろうと→
He tries to understand others' pain…
相手は　こっちの痛みなど
知ろうとはしない。
but they do not even attempt
to know our pain.
そして　この世界もまた
そんなことを望んでいない。
Furthermore, this world has
no desire for that either.
それが現実だ。
That is reality.
輪廻眼を持つお前なら
それを理解できるはずだ。
You possess the Rinnegan,
so you should understand.
アンタが何を言おうと
俺は弥彦の理想を信じる！
No matter what you say,
I believe in Yahiko's ideals!
痛みが伴わなければ
現実を実感できんか？
I guess without pain…
you cannot experience reality.
そういうところは
輪廻眼を持とうと→
In that respect, even though
you possess the Rinnegan,
お前も凡人だな　長門。
you still think like
an average person.
よかろう　真実を見極めろ。
自らの痛みとともにな。
Very well…
Go see reality for yourself,
and experience pain.
ここにいたのか　長門。
弥彦。
There you are, Nagato.
Yahiko…
誰かいたのか？
Was someone just here?
いや…。
No…
そろそろ出発しよう。
Let's get going.
半蔵様との会合に遅れちまう。
Or we'll be late for the meeting
with Lord Hanzo.
うん　行こう！
Right, let's go!
イテェ！　何だよ　人が気持よく
寝てるってのに　まったく！
Oww!
What's the big idea?
I was having a nice nap!
なになに？
What?
おい　弥彦と長門の兄貴は！？
Hey! Where'd Brothers Yahiko
and Nagato go?!
もう　出かけたんじゃないのか？
I think they left already.
今日は半蔵との…。
The meeting with Hanzo is today.
みんなを叩き起こせ！
Wake the guys up!
We have to catch up with them!
兄貴たちのあとを追うぞ！
What's wrong?
どうした！？
わけはあとで話す！
I'll tell you later!
おい　いったい何があった！？
What's going on anyway?
木ノ葉国境付近にいる→
We just received word
メンバーから連絡が入った。
from a member of
the Hidden Leaf border team.
木ノ葉の暗部の部隊が→
The Leaf's ANBU Black Ops are
on their way to Hanzo's as well.
半蔵の元に向かったってな！
えっ　木ノ葉の暗部？
The Leaf's ANBU?
なんで連中が半蔵のとこに？
Why are they going to Hanzo's?
詳しいことは　わからねえ！
I don't know the specifics.
だが　イヤなタイミングじゃねえかよ。
But I just don't like the timing
of it all, you know?
それに　よく考えてみりゃ→
And when you think about it…
半蔵の話ってのも→
this thing with Hanzo just sounds
too good to be true.
うますぎる気がする！
Then that means...
today's meeting with Hanzo is…
それじゃ　今日の半蔵との会合…。
とにかく兄貴たちの
耳に入れておかねえと！
Whatever it is,
we need to let Brothers know!
残念だが　ここから先に
お前たちを通すわけにはいかん。
As much as I regret it,
I can't let you go any further.
誰だ！？
Who are you?!
俺の名は　うちはマダラ。
My name is Madara Uchiha…
キサマ　半蔵の差し金か！？
Damn you! Did Hanzo send you?
半蔵の仲間ではないが→
I don't work for Hanzo.
今　お前たちによけいな
手出しをされては困る。
But I can't let you interfere right now.
俺は長門に現実を知って
もらわなきゃならないんでな。
I want Nagato to see
what reality is.
何のことかわかんねえが
時間がねえ！
We don't have time for
your nonsense.
コイツを叩きのめせ！
（みんな）おお～っ！
Kill them!
ザコは任せた。
You take care of the weaklings.
You sure like to order me around!
（ゼツ）まったく
人使いが荒いんだから。
韋駄天の鳩助！
I'm Kyusuke the Swift!
Don't underestimate my speed!
俺の足を
なめてもらっちゃ困るぜ！
うお～！
I slipped right through him?
すり抜けた。
いったいどうなって…。
What's going on?!
鳩助！
Kyusuke!
テメエら　なんで　こんな　ことを…。
You bastards!
Why…are you…doing this?
長門の輪廻眼を
本当の意味で開眼させる。
I'm going to awaken Nagato's Rinnegan
in the truest sense possible.
なんのことだ？
What're you talking about?
この呪われた世界に
本当の平和など存在しない。
There is no such thing as peace
in this accursed world.
長門は今の理想を捨て
新たな世界に旅立つ。
Nagato must abandon this dream
and set out into a new world.
I'm not going to let you!
そうはいくかよ！
大仏　俺ごとやれ！
Daibutsu!
Now! Go right through me!
ぐっ…。
早く！
Hurry!
あの世で会おうぞ！
I'll see you in the next world!
はっ！
水牢の術か。
この程度の術で　俺はやれんぞ。
The Water Prison Jutsu?
You can't beat me with a jutsu like this!
《ただの水牢じゃねえ》
This is no ordinary Water Prison.
《これはセメント》
This is cement!
《戦争孤児だった俺の
やさぐれた人生の中で→
For the first time in
my dismal life as a war orphan…
I found hope in the Akatsuki!
暁は初めて見た希望だったんだ。
それを　テメエなんかに奪われて
たまるかよ！》
You think…I'd let some bastard
like you take that away?!
《捨て身の攻撃なのだろうが→
He's sacrificing his life
in this attack…
お前とでは
文字どおり次元が違う》
But, as expected,
we're literally in different dimensions.
そんな…。
No way!
鳩助　お前の死はムダには…。
Kyusuke…
Your death will not be…
イタタタ…　固まった表皮が
剥けちゃって　ヒリヒリするよ。
Owww…
The outer skin hardened…
and peeled off, and it stings!
悪いが　お前たちは全員
ここで始末する。
Sorry, but this is the end for all of you.
大丈夫か？
ああ。
Are you okay?
Yeah.
さあ　急ぐぞ。
長門の運命を見届ける。
Come, we have to hurry!
We have to witness Nagato's destiny!
（半蔵）弥彦。　リーダーのお前には
ここで死んでもらう。
Yahiko…
You are the leader,
so you must die.
抵抗すれば　この女の命はない。
If you resist, this woman will die.
そこの赤い髪のお前
それで弥彦を殺せ。
You! The red-haired one.
Use that to kill Yahiko.
そうすれば
女とお前は助けてやる。
Then I will spare you and the woman.
やめて長門。　私のことはいいから
２人ともここから逃げて！
Don't, Nagato!
Never mind me!
Both of you escape!
Nagato.
（弥彦）長門。
俺を殺れ。
Kill me.
長門！
やめて！
Nagato!
No!
早くしろ。
この女が死んでもいいのか？
Hurry it up.
Or do you want this woman to die?!
小南…。
Konan…
弥彦…。
Yahi—
小南と　なんとしてでも
生き延びろ。
You and Konan…must survive,
no matter what it takes.
お前は　この世の救世主だ。
You are…
the savior…of this world.
お前だったら　本当に…。
I know…you can…
do it.
Yahiko!
弥彦！
やれ！
Kill them!
弾いただと！？
どうやって？
He repelled it!
How?!
やったか。
Did we get him?
長門。
小南。
Nagato…
Konan, hold onto Yahiko
and stay still.
弥彦を抱いて　じっとしていろ。
やるな　小僧。
Not bad, kid!
わしの火遁を食らいながら
逃げきるとは。
You escaped even while being hit
by my Fire Style Jutsu!
お前　ただのガキではないな
その眼。
You're…no ordinary kid.
Those eyes…
やれ！
Get him!
口寄せ　外道魔像！
Summoning Jutsu!
Gedo Statue!
（みんな）ぐわぁ～！
おっ　出た！
呼んだか。
There it is!
So he summoned it.
It's the Ten Tails' husk…
十尾の抜け殻。
なんだ　あれは。
What…is that?!
長門　これは使っちゃダメ！
Nagato... No! Don't use that!
うおぉ～！！
ぐわぁ！
あれに触れたら死ぬぞ！
うわぁ！
We're dead if that touches us!
うおぉ～！！
お前が　カゲのリーダーだったようだな。
So you were the leader
behind the scenes.
輪廻眼を持っていようとは
驚かされたわ。
It's quite a surprise that
you possess the Rinnegan.
長門…。
Nagato…
うおぉ～！！
瞬身の術！
Teleportation Jutsu!
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
長門　弥彦　小南。
Nagato, Yahiko, Konan…
夢の世界　そこで
また会わせてやる　必ず。
The world of dreams…
I shall let you see each other there…
without fail.
俺の言ったとおりだったろ。
Didn't I say so?
（長門）ああ　やっとわかったよ。
Yeah, I finally understand.
平和を保ちたいとする
利己的な意思が戦争を起こし→
The selfish desire to
preserve peace causes war.
愛を守るために
憎しみが生まれる。
この呪われた世界に
本当の平和など存在しない。
そのとおりだ。
暁は　永遠にキミがリーダーだ。
弥彦。
皆様　お変わりございませんか？
美空ひばりです。
では　最後まで
ごゆっくりお楽しみください。
（宮本）『木曜８時のコンサート　名曲！
にっぽんの歌』　２時間スペシャル。
（松丸）今回も
豪華な歌手の皆さんによる→